Guide to the Rosalinda Guillén and Joseph Moore Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
Guide to the Rosalinda Guillén and Joseph Moore papers
1982-2011
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
5799
Guillén, Rosalinda,$d1950?-
20.54 cubic feet plus 1 oversize folder 19 boxes
Records relating to union organizers/Rainbow Coalition members Joseph Moore and Rosalinda Guillén
Rosalinda Guillén was born in Texas, grew up in Mexico, and moved to Washington State with her family at age 10 in 1960, working as part of the migrant farm labor community in the northwest for much of the next decade. She then worked at Skagit State Bank for 16 years, but quit only four years before she was eligible to retire in order to organize farm labor for the United Farm Workers of America (UFW).
Guillén's training as a community organizer came from being recruited by the Rainbow Coalition to mobilize support in Washington State for Reverend Jesse Jackson’s 1988 presidential campaign. It was through that work that she learned about farm workers who were organizing at Chateau Ste. Michelle, Washington’s largest winery, and got so involved that she became one of the campaign’s lead organizers. From from Fall of 1993 to December 5, 1995, she ran the grassroots worker organizing campaign, which resulted in the first union contract for farm workers in Washington state.
Following that victory, Guillén went on to serve in a number of high-level UFW organizing jobs, including the coordinator of a strawberry-picker organizing drive in California's Salinas Valley, and the national organization's Northwest Regional Director, Policy Director, Executive Board Member, and finally National Vice-President. Following her work for the UFW, she served as the Executive Director of La Unión del Pueblo Entero (LUPE), a non-profit organization founded by Cesar Chavez.
Currently, Guillén serves as the Affirmative Action Chair of the Whatcom County Democrats, and is the co-founder of and Executive Director for Community to Community Development (C2C), a “a place-based, grassroots organization committed to creating alliances in order to strengthen local and global movements towards social, economic and environmental justice” in Bellingham, Washington.
[Rosalinda Guillén nació en Texas y creció en México. A los 10 años en el año 1960, se mudó al estado de Washington con su familia, donde trabajaba como parte de la comunidad de trabajadores agrícolas migrantes en el noroeste por mucha de la próxima década. Luego trabajó para Skagit State Bank por 16 años, dejando ese trabajo sólo 4 años antes de que fuera elegible para retirarse para organizar trabajadores agrícolas con United Farm Workers of America (UFW).
Guillén fue reclutada y entrenada como organizadora comunitaria por Rainbow Coalition para movilizar soporte en el estado de Washington para la campaña presidencial del Reverendo Jesse Jackson en 1988. Fue por ese trabajo que aprendió Guillén de los trabajadores agrícolas quienes estaban organizando en Chateau Ste. Michelle, la bodega de vinos mas grande en Washington. Llegó a involucrarse tanto que llegó a ser una organizadora principal de la campaña. Desde el otoño 1993 hasta el 5 de diciembre 1995, ella manejo la campaña de organizar el base de trabajadores que resultó en el primer contrato para trabajadores agrícolas en el estado de Washington.
Siguiendo esa victoria, Guillén pasó a servir en varios trabajos de alto nivel con UFW, incluyendo como coordinadora del empujo para organizar recolectores de fresas en el Valle de Salinas en California, Directora Regional del Noroeste al nivel nacional, Directora de Póliza, Miembra de la Junta Ejecutiva, y finalmente como Vicepresidente Nacional. Siguiendo su trabajo con UFW, ella sirvió como Directora Ejecutiva de La Unión del Pueblo Entero (LUPE), una organización sin fines de lucro fundado por Cesar Chavez.
Ahora Guillén sirve como Presidente de Acción Afirmativa de los Democratas de Whatcom County y es la Co-Fundadora y Directora Ejecutiva de Community to Community Development (C2C), una “organización de base local comprometido a crear alianzas para fortalecer los movimientos locales y globales hacia justicia social, económica y ambiental” en Bellingham, Washington.]
Organized into 2 accessions.
Accession No. 5799-001, Rosalinda Guillen and Joseph Moore Papers [Guía A Los Archivos De Rosalinda Guillen Y Joseph Moore], 1982-2011
Accession No. 5799-002, Rosalinda Guillen and Joseph Moore papers, 1990s
Records relating to Joseph Moore and Rosalinda Guillén's roles as organizers for the Rainbow Coalition in Washington State during Jesse Jackson's 1988 presidential campaign and the campaign to organize farm workers at Chateau Ste. Michelle (Washington’s largest winery) between 1993 and 1995. Records also document Guillén's role as an organizer for the United Farm Workers in a strawberry-picker organizing drive in California's Salinas Valley, as the national organization's Northwest Regional Director, Policy Director, Executive Board Member, and finally National Vice-President.
[Alcance y Contenido: Archivos relacionados a los papeles de Joseph Moore y Rosalinda Guillén como organizadores de la Coalición Arco Iris en el estado de Washington durante la campaña presidencial de Jesse Jackson en 1988 y la campaña para organizar a los trabajadores agrícolas en Chateau Ste. Michelle (la bodega más grande del estado de Washington) desde 1993 hasta 1995. Los registros documentan el papel de Guillén como una de los organizadores del United Farm Workers [Sindicato Unido de Campesinos] en la campaña por organizar a los recolectores de fresas en Salinas Valley, California; y como Directora Regional del Noroeste, Directora de Política, Miembro del Consejo Ejecutivo, y finalmente, Vicepresidente Nacional de dicha organización.]
Forms part of the Labor Archives of Washington.
Records are stored offsite; advance notice required for use.
[Acceso Físico/Técnico: Registros se embodegan fuera del precio; se requiere aviso para usarlos.]
Open to all users. [Restricciónes de Acceso: Abierto para todos los usuarios].
The visual materials that form part of this collection are described and indexed in guide to the
.
Guillén, Rosalinda,$d1950?- $vArchives; Moore, Joseph,$d1932- $vArchives; Moore, Joseph,$d1932-; National Rainbow Coalition (U.S.)$xCampaigns.; United Farm Workers of America.; Chateau Ste. Michelle (Winery)$xEmployees.; Chateau Ste. Michelle (Winery)$xManagement.; Labor Archives of Washington State (University of Washington),; Labor unions$zWashington (State); Labor unions$zCalifornia.; Labor$zWashington (State); Labor$zCalifornia.; Labor movement$zWashington (State); Labor movement$zCalifornia.
Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Labor History; Labor Unions; Political Campaigns; Politics and Politicians; Washington (State)
- Rosalinda Guillén and Joseph Moore Papers [Guía A Los Archivos De Rosalinda Guillén Y Joseph Moore], 1982-2011; 5799-001; 20.54 cubic feet [Cantidad: 20.54 Pies Cúbicos] 19 boxes [19 cajas]
  Records relating to Joseph Moore and Rosalinda Guillén's roles as organizers for the Rainbow Coalition in Washington State during Jesse Jackson's 1988 presidential campaign and the campaign to organize farm workers at Chateau Ste. Michelle (Washington’s largest winery) between 1993 and 1995. Records also document Guillén's role as an organizer for the United Farm Workers in a strawberry-picker organizing drive in California's Salinas Valley, as the national organization's Northwest Regional Director, Policy Director, Executive Board Member, and finally National Vice-President.
  [Alcance y Contenido: Los registros relativos a los roles de Joseph Moore y Rosalinda Guillén como organizadores de la Coalición Rainbow en el estado de Washington durante la campaña Presidencial de Jesse Jackson en 1988 y la campaña para organizar a los trabajadores agrícolas en el “Chateau Ste. Michelle” (La Mayor Bodega de Washington) entre 1993 y 1995. Los registros también documentan el papel de Guillén como organizador de la Unión De Campesinos en una unidad de recolección de fresa campaña oraganizada en Salinas Valley en California, como Director Regional del Noroeste de la Organización Nacional, Director de Política, Miembro del Consejo Ejecutivo Y, finalmente, Vicepresidente Nacional.]
  Open to all users. [Restricciones De Acceso: Abierto Para Todos Los Usuarios.]
  Donors: Rosalinda Guillén and Joseph Moore, June 13, 2013. [Información De Adquisición: Donadores: Rosalinda Guillén y Joseph Moore, Junio 13, 2013.]
  - Washington State Rainbow Coalition [Coalición Rainbow del Estado de Washington.], 1988-1992 (Box-folder 1/1)
  - Rainbow Coalition [Coalición Rainbow], 1989-1995 (Box-folder 1/2)
  - Rainbow Coalition - Rosalinda Guillén on Earthbound Televisión [Coalición Rainbow- Rosalinda Guillén en Televisión Terrestre], 1992 (Box-folder 1/3)
  - Rainbow Coalition - Political Action Task Force [Coalición Rainbow - Cuerpo Especial de Medidas Políticas ], 2005 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Rainbow Coalition - Whatcom County [Coalición Rainbow - Condado de Whatcom], 2005 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Rainbow Coalition - Whatcom County Rainbow Coalition: Chapter X By-Laws [Coalición Rainbow - Coalición Rainbow Del Condado De Whatcom: Capítulo X Estatutos Sociales], 1988 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - UFW California - Endorsements - Political Report, Endorsed Candidates [UFW California – La Aprobación - Informe Político, Candidatos Respaldados], 1998 (Box-folder 1/7)
  - UFW California - Endorsements - Candidate Scorecards [UFW California - La Aprobación – Tarjeta De Puntajes De Un Candidato], 1998-2000 (Box-folder 1/8)
  - UFW California - Endorsements - Candidate Scorecards [UFW California - La Aprobación – Tarjeta de Puntajes de un Candidato], 1998 (Box-folder 1/9)
  - UFW California - Endorsements - Get Out the Vote [UFW California - La Aprobación - Emitir el Voto.], 1998 (Box-folder 1/10)
  - UFW - California - Agricultural Labor Relation Act Press Conference [UFW - California - Conferencia de Prensa sobre laLey de Relaciones del Trabajo Agrícola], 1999 (Box-folder 1/11)
  - UFW California - Endorsements - Sample Notification of Endorsement Letter [UFW California - La Aprobación - Notificación Muestra de la Carta de Aprobación], 1999 (Box-folder 1/12)
  - UFW California - Endorsements - Endorsement Process Notes [UFW California - La Aprobación – Notas del Proceso de Aprobación.], 1999-2000 (Box-folder 1/13)
  - UFW California - Endorsements - Forms: Endorsement Process Summary [UFW California - La Aprobación - Formularios: Resumen Del Proceso De Aprobaciones], 1999-2000 (Box-folder 1/14)
  - UFW California - Endorsements - Endorsement Workshop Training Materials [UFW California - Apoyo - Materiales de Entrenamiento Para el Taller de Aprobación], c. 1999-2000 (Box-folder 1/15)
  - UFW California - Endorsements - Training Material - Comite De Base [UFW California - La Aprobación – Material De Entrenamiento – Comité De Base], c. 1999-2000 (Box-folder 1/16)
  - UFW California - Endorsements - Endorsement Process Notes [UFW California - La Aprobación - Notas Del Proceso De La Aprobación], 2000-2001 (Box-folder 1/17)
  - UFW California - Endorsements - Board Polls [UFW California - La Aprobación – Encuesta Electoral], 2000-2001 (Box-folder 1/18)
  - UFW California - Endorsements - Willie C. Velasquez Institute [UFW California - La Aprobación - Instituto De Willie C. Velásquez], 2000-2002 (Box-folder 1/19)
  - UFW California - Endorsements - Candidate Endorsement [UFW California - La Aprobación – Aprobación del Candidato], 2000-2002 (Box-folder 1/20)
  - UFW California - Endorsements - Labor Endorsements [UFW California - La Aprobación – Respaldo Del Trabajo], 2000 (Box-folder 1/21)
  - UFW California - Endorsements - Endorsement/Campaign Analysis [UFW California - La Aprobación - Aprobación /Análisis de Campaña.], 2000 (Box-folder 1/22)
  - UFW California - Endorsements - Candidate Scorecards & Voting Records [UFW California - La Aprobación - Tarjeta De Puntajes De Un Candidato Y Registro De Votos], 2000-2002 (Box-folder 1/23)
  - UFW California - Little Hoover Commission [UFW California - Comisión "Little Hoover"], 2001 (Box-folder 1/24)
  - UFW California - Endorsements - Los Angeles Municipal Elections [UFW California - La Aprobación - Elecciónes Municipales De Los Angeles], 2001 (Box-folder 1/25)
  - UFW California - Endorsements - Labor Council for Latin American Advancement [UFW California - La Aprobación - Consejo del Trabajo Para el Avance Latinoamericano], 2001-2002 (Box-folder 1/26)
  - UFW California - Political - Agricultural Labor Relations Board Cuts [UFW California - Políticos - Los Recortes de la Junta de Relaciones del Trabajo Agrícola], 2001-2002 (Box-folder 1/27)
  - UFW California - Endorsements - Field [UFW California - La Aprobación – Campo], 2002 (Box-folder 1/28)
  - UFW California - Endorsements - Endorsement Results California Primary [UFW California - La Aprobación – Aprobación De Los Resultados Primarios De California], 2002 (Box-folder 1/29)
  - UFW California - Endorsements - Get Out the Vote [UFW California - La Aprobación - Emitir El Voto], 2002 (Box-folder 1/30)
  - UFW California - Endorsements - Election Day Weekend [UFW California - La Aprobación - Día De Las Elecciones En Fin De Semana], November 1, 2002-November 5, 2002 (Box-folder 1/31)
  - UFW California - Endorsements - Get Out the Vote Primaries [UFW California - La Aprobación - Fuera Las Primarias De Voto], 2002 (Box-folder 1/32)
  - Farmworker Solidarity March - News Clippings [Marcha de Solidaridad Campesina - Recortes de Prensa], 1992-2004 (Box-folder 1/33)
  - Farmworker Solidarity March - Planning Materials, Photo [Marcha de Solidaridad Campesina - Materiales de Planeación, Foto], 2000 (Box-folder 1/34)
  - Farmworker Solidarity March - Planning Materials [Marcha de Solidaridad Campesina - Materiales de Planeación], 2000-2003 (Box-folder 1/35)
  - Farmworkers Solidarity March [Marcha de Solidaridad Campesina], 1992 (Box-folder 1/36)
  - Farm Worker Solidarity March - Planning Materials [Marcha de Solidaridad Campesina - Materiales de Planeación], 2002-2004 (Box-folder 1/37)
  - Farm Worker Solidarity March - Planning Committee Materials [Marcha de Solidaridad Campesina - Materiales de Planeación del Comité], 2003-2004 (Box-folder 1/38)
  - Farmworker Solidarity March - Peacekeeper Training [Marcha de Solidaridad Campesina - Capacitación de Pacificadores], c. 2004 (Box-folder 1/39)
  - Farmworker Solidarity March - Photographs [Marcha de Solidaridad Campesina - Fotos], 2004 (Box-folder 1/40)
  - Farmworker Solidarity march - Planning Materials [Marcha de Solidaridad Campesina - Materiales De Planeación.], 2004 (Box-folder 1/41)
  - Farmworker Solidarity March - News Clippings [Marcha de Solidaridad Campesina - Recortes de Noticias], 2004 (Box-folder 1/42)
  - Farmworker Solidarity March - Petition to Skagit & Whatcom Commissioners [Marcha de Solidaridad Campesina - Petición al Condado de Skagit y Comisionados de Whatcom], 2005 (Box-folder 1/43)
  - Farm Worker Solidarity March - Planning Committee Materials [Marcha de Solidaridad Campesina - Materiales De Planeación Del Comité], 2004-2005 (Box-folder 1/44)
  - Farm Worker Solidarity March - Planning - House Meetings [Marcha de Solidaridad Campesina - Planeación - Juntas De La Casa], 2004 (Box-folder 1/45)
  - Farm Worker Solidarity March - Change for Change Event [Marcha de Solidaridad Campesina - Evento Del Cambio Por El Cambio], 2004 (Box-folder 1/46)
  - UFW Washington - Events - Newsclippings [UFW Washington - Eventos - Recortes de Prensa], 1995-1997 (Box-folder 1/47)
  - UFW Washington - LA Opinion Article & Conference Speaking Materials [UFW Washington - LA Artículo de Opinión & Materiales de Discursos en Conferencias], 1996-2001 (Box-folder 1/48)
  - Labor Conference on Affirmative Action Conference [Conferencia De Trabajo Sobre La Conferencia De Acción Afirmativa], 1996 (Box-folder 1/49)
  - Labor Education & Research Center Conference Speaking Materials [Educación Laboral y Materiales De Conferencia Del Centro De Investigación], 1992-1996 (Box-folder 1/50)
  - Miguel Guillén Speech for "Whispering Walls" Art Installation to Aztlan Rising Course at Skagit Valley College [El Discurso De Miguel Guillén "Susurrando Paredes" Arte Situada a la Creciente Aztlan Camino al Colegio del Valle del Condado de Skagit], 2001 (Box-folder 1/51)
  - "Sustaining the City: Symposium Celebrating Tilth's 20th Anniversary," Rosalinda Guillén Speaking Materials ["Mantener La Ciudad: Simposio De La Celebración Del 20 Aniversario De Labranza," Menciona Rosalinda Guillén], 1994 (Box-folder 1/52)
  - AFL-CIO Political Directors' Meeting [Junta de los Directores Políticos de AFL-CIO], 12-Feb-01 (Box-folder 1/53)
  - Conferences & Correspondence - Evergreen State College [Conferencias & Correspondencia - Colegio Del Estado De Evergreen.], 1994-1996 (Box-folder 1/54)
  - UFW Washington - Rally & March [UFW Washington - Reunión y Marcha.], September 6, 1992 (Box-folder 1/55)
  - Correspondence - California Correctional Peace Officiers Association [Correspondencia - Asociación de Funcionarios Penitenciarios de Paz en California], 2001 (Box-folder 1/56)
  - Correspondence - California Occupational Health & Safety Commission [Correspondencia - Comisión de Salud y Comisión de Seguridad de California], 2003 (Box-folder 1/57)
  - Projeto Dom Helder Camara Calendars [Proyecto Dom Helder Calendarios De Cámara], January 2005-December 2005 (Box-folder 2/1)
  - Winter Calendar [Calendario de Invierno], January 2004-December 2004 (Box-folder 2/2)
  - Fax Correspondence: Short Term Legislative Plan [Correspondencia de Fax: Plan Legislativo a Corto Plazo], June 12, 2001 (Box-folder 2/3)
  - UFW California - Professional Associations of Farm Labor Contractors and Custom Harvesters Contact List [UFW California - Asociaciónes de los Contratistas de Labor Agrícola y Lista de Contactos de los Cosechadores a Medida], April 12, 2002 (Box-folder 2/4)
  - UFW California -Article:Interpersonal Communication Tops Concerns of Farm Supervisors [California UFW - Artículo: La Comunicación Interpersonal Encabeza Las Preocupaciones De Los Supervisores De La Granja], September 2001-October 2001 (Box-folder 2/5)
  - UFW California -Request for Information: California Division of Labor Standards Enforcement's (DLSE) Role in Agricultural Enforcement [UFW California - Solicitúd De Información: División Del Papel Del Cumplimiento De Normas Laborales En Ejecución Agrícola De California], June 19, 2000-June 14, 2001 (Box-folder 2/6)
  - UFW California -California Research Bureau's Farmworker Legislation Summary, 1975-2000 [UFW California - Resumen De La Legislación De Los Trabajadores Agrícolas De La Agencia De Investigación De California, 1975-2000], c. 2000 (Box-folder 2/7)
  - Correspondence: FLC Bills (AB 423, AB 638, SB 1125) [Correspondencia: FLC Facturas], April 2, 2001-April 13, 2001 (Box-folder 2/8)
  - Survey: The 2000 Central Valley Raisin & Grape Harvests [Estudio: Las Cosechas de Pasas & Uvas de la Central Valley de 2000], February 2001 (Box-folder 2/9)
  - "Farm Labor Contractors Issue Development:" Articles, Analysis, & Correspondence ["Desarrollo de los Problemas de los Contratistas de Labor Agrícola:" Artículos, Análisis, y Correspondencia], June 14, 2001-August 2002 (Box-folder 2/10)
  - Center for the Study of Urban Poverty: Day Laborers in Southern California [El Centro del Investigación para el Estudio de la Pobreza Urbana: Los Jornaleros del Sur de California], May 30, 1999 (Box-folder 2/11)
  - Farm Labor Contractors Issue Development: Correspondence and Notes [Desarrollo de los Problemas de los Contratistas de Labor Agrícola: Correspondencia y Notas], June 21, 2001-June 13, 2002 (Box-folder 2/12)
  - Agricultural Affairs Committee: Bill Texts & Letter [Comité de Actividades Agricultural: Textos de Cuentas y Carteras], April 23, 2001-June 14, 2001 (Box-folder 2/13)
  - Legislative Agenda 2003: Correspondence, Memorandums, Notes, and Possible Legislation [Agenda Legislativa del 2003: Correspondencia, Memorandos, Notas y Posible Legislación], January 9, 1999-March 15, 2003 (Box-folder 2/14)
  - Opt-Out Language (Berkeley): Hospitality Industry Employment Standards [El Lenguaje De Darse De Baja (Berkeley): Los Estándares de Empleo en la Industria de la Hospitalidad], Undated (Box-folder 2/15)
  - AG Industry Tax Moratorium: Correspondence, Legislation, Memorandums, and Press [Suspensión de Impuestos de la Industria AG: Correspondencia, Legislación, Memorandos y Prensa], January 23, 2003-June 16, 2003 (Box-folder 2/16)
  - Driver's License California 2003: Action Plan, Correspondence, Legislation, and Press [Licencia de Conducir en California en 2003: Plan de Acción, Correspondencia, Legislación, y la Prensa], July 7, 1999-February 11, 2003 (Box-folder 2/17)
  - Minimum Wage Campaign 2002: Correspondence [Campaña para Aumentar el Salario Mínimo en el 2002: Correspondencia], December 18, 2001-February 21, 2003 (Box-folder 2/18)
  - Consumers for Auto Reliability and Safety: Correspondence and Press [Consumidores Para Auto Confiabilidad y Seguridad: Correspondencia y Prensa], June 30, 1999-January 30, 2003 (Box-folder 2/19)
  - Farm Worker Movement Leadership: Agricultural Issues, Guiding Principles, and Engagement Opportunities [El liderato del Movimiento de los Campesinos: Problemas de la Agricultura, Principios Rectores, y Oportunidades de Contratación], April 28, 1995-September 25, 2000 (Box-folder 2/20)
  - Farm Labor: Press Coverage [Labor Agricola: Cobertura de los Medios], January 2001-May 2001 (Box-folder 2/21)
  - Fresno Bee Special Report: Season in the Sun [Informe Especial de Fresno: "Temporada Solar"], May 13, 2001 (Box-folder 2/22)
  - Farm Labor: Overview, Profile, & Union Disputes [Trabajadores Agrícolas: Visión General, Perfil, Y Disputas De La Unión], c. 1998-October 9, 2001 (Box-folder 2/23)
  - Farm Labor: Correspondence, Memorandums, Studies, and White Papers [Trabajadores Agrícolas: Correspondencia, Memorandos, Estudios y Libros Blancos.], c. 1995-January 14, 2000 (Box-folder 2/24)
  - Farm Labor Legislation: Correspondence, Memorandums, & Summaries [Trabajadores Agrícolas: Correspondencia, Memorandos, y Resúmenes], February 1999-February 19, 2002 (Box-folder 2/25)
  - Strawberry Campaign: Correspondence, Press, Memorandums, & Summaries [Campaña de la Fresa: Correspondencia, Prensa, Memorandos, y Resúmenes], April 2, 1997-July 20, 1998 (Box-folder 2/26)
  - Texas Politics: Correspondence, Memorandums, and Press [Políticas del Estado de Texas: La Correspondencia, Memorandos y Prensa], July 28, 1999-January 8, 2003 (Box-folder 2/27)
  - Texas Labor Code [Códigos Laboral del Estado de Texas], February 2, 1999-March 10, 1999 (Box-folder 2/28)
  - AB-423/ SB-1125: Correspondence, Memorandums, Summaries, & Press [AB-423/ SB- 1125: Correspondencia, Memorandos, Resúmenes, y Prensa], August 2001-April 4, 2002 (Box-folder 2/29)
  - AB-423: Materials (en español) [AB-423 Materiales en Español], April 23, 2001-August 13, 2001 (Box-folder 2/30)
  - Farm Labor Contractor Bills: Final Analysis, Press, & Government Statements [Programa de Contratación de Trabajadores Agrícolas: Análisis Final, de Prensa, y Órganos de Gobierno], August 2001 (Box-folder 2/31)
  - SB-1125: Analysis, Fact Sheet, & Legislation Digest [SB-1125: Análisis, Hoja Informativa, y Resumen de Legislación], February 23, 2001-July 7, 2001 (Box-folder 2/32)
  - Chronology of United Farm Workers-Coastal Berry Company Election [Cronología de los Trabajadores Agrícolas Unidos - Elección de la Empresa de “Baya Costera”], June 14, 1999 (Box-folder 2/33)